urbanoutfitters.co.uk 2012-12-25

# Urban Outfitters - Privacy & Security Policy

Skip to content

Please enter a valid postcode e.g. 

PRIVACY & SECURITY POLICY

Ensuring the privacy and security of your personal information is very important to us. Our Privacy & Security Policy outlines the information we collect about you, how we use, disclose and otherwise manage this information and the choices you have to restrict our usage of this information.

COLLECTED INFORMATION  
We collect personal information when you sign up for Urban Outfitters Europe or our email mailing list; or contact us with a comment, question or complaint. This may include, for example, your name, date of birth, email address, postal address, telephone number, whether you are male or female and your product preferences.

OUR EMAIL LIST  
When you sign-up to receive our emailing list, we may also collect optional information such as your name, post code, and product interests. We use this personal information to tailor our email messages and to enhance our product and service offerings.

CUSTOMER SERVICE  
When you contact us with a question, feedback or other comment, you may be asked for information that identifies you, such as your name, address and telephone number. We collect this information to verify your identity and to help us promptly answer your question or respond to your comment or feedback. We may retain this information to assist you in the future. We also may use your feedback, suggestions and comments to monitor and/or improve our products or website.

WEBSITE INFORMATION COLLECTED  
You can visit this site (www.urbanoutfitters.co.uk) without telling us who you are or providing us with any personal information. However, we collect the IP (Internet protocol) addresses of all our website visitors and other related information such as page requests, browser type, operating system and average time spent on our website. We use this information to monitor and improve our website.  
We use cookies and similar technologies to collect information about the pages you access or visit. Cookies are bits of information that are automatically stored on your computer so we can recognise you when you return. We use cookies to better understand your use of the Urban Outfitters Europe website so that we may continue to refine and improve the website. If you do not wish to have cookies on your system, you can set your browser preferences to disable them. However, if you decide not to accept cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of all of the features on the Urban Outfitters Europe website. The information collected through cookies may be combined with other identifiable personal information (such as demographic information) from our records and other sources. We may use this combined information for future marketing initiatives and to help us improve our website presentation.

INFORMATION WE SHARE  
We may transfer (or otherwise make available) your personal information to other members of the Urban Outfitters corporate family and other third parties who provide services on our behalf. We may use service providers to process data, host our website, and send emails, in order to help us better understand your use of our website and refine and improve the website. These companies may store and process this information in the United Kingdom or United States.  
All of our service providers are required to maintain the confidentiality and security of your personal information and to use it only in compliance with applicable privacy laws. These companies are not authorised to use your information in any manner, other than in helping us to provide you with products and services or as otherwise required by applicable law. At various times we may also ask you whether you would be happy for your personal information to be shared with other companies that are not associated with the Urban Outfitters corporate family. Where you agree to this, once we have shared your personal information with those other companies, this Privacy & Security Policy will not apply to their use of your personal information and their own policies will apply.  
We may also disclose specific personal information about you if required by law, governmental request or court order if, based on our good faith belief, it is necessary to conform or comply with such law, request or court order.  
At various times we may also ask you whether you would be happy for your personal information to be shared with other companies which are not associated with the Anthropologie corporate family. Where you agree to this, once we have shared your personal information with those other companies, this Privacy & Security Policy will not apply to their use of your personal information and their own policies will apply.

SALE OF BUSINESS  
Urban Outfitters Europe may transfer any information we have about you in the event of a merger with a third party or upon a sale or transfer of all or a portion of our business or assets to a third party acquirer.

RETENTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
We only keep your personal information as long as necessary for the purposes we collected it, or as otherwise required by law.

SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
Your privacy is important to us. We maintain reasonable administrative, technical and physical safeguards in an effort to protect against the loss, theft, unauthorised access, use, modification and disclosure of personal information in our custody and control. We have implemented measures in an effort to safeguard the personal information in our custody and control, including only providing access to personal information to employees and authorised service providers who require such information for the purposes described in this Privacy & Security Policy. To provide you with an increased level of security, online access to certain personal information may be protected with a password you select. We strongly recommend that you do not disclose your password to anyone. We will never ask you for your password in any unsolicited communication.

POLICY CHANGES  
We may periodically update this Privacy & Security Policy for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed. Any changes made will be posted here. We will treat your personal information in accordance with the Privacy & Security Policy in place at the time your information was collected.  
This Privacy & Security Policy was updated on 10 September 2010 to take account of your ability to agree to us sharing your personal information with other companies that are not associated with the Urban Outfitters corporate family.

CONTACT US  
Feel free to contact us with any questions about our Privacy & Security Policy or the manner in which we treat your personal information or to withdraw your name from an email or other marketing list.  
If you wish to access or update the personal information we have about you, or to correct factual errors in our records, please contact us as set out below. To protect your privacy, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.  
EMAIL: [UrbanEuropeCS@urbanout.com](mailto:UrbanEuropeCS@urbanout.com) [UrbanEuropeCS@urbanout.com](mailto:UrbanEuropeCS@urbanout.com)   
MAIL: Urban Outfitters Europe, Stephenson Harwood, 1 St Paul's Churchyard, London EC4M 8SH  
Urban Outfitters Europe is a trading name of URBN UK Limited, a UK registered company (company number 3124253 and VAT number 6325757B), whose registered office address is: Stephenson Harwood, 1 St Pauls Churchyard, London EC4M 8SH

URBAN OUTFITTERS EMAIL SUBSCRIPTIONS  
If you have chosen to receive emails from Urban Outfitters Europe, we will offer you advanced notice of sales, new merchandise, store openings and other Urban Outfitters Europe news. Email addresses provided to Urban Outfitters Europe are only used internally for the purpose of sending you communication from Urban Outfitters Europe. We respect your privacy rights and will not sell or rent your email address to other companies. If you would like to unsubscribe from our email list, please contact us at [UrbanEuropeCS@urbanout.com](mailto:UrbanEuropeCS@urbanout.com). You may also click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our emails. We will remove your name from our email list as soon as possible. Please recognize that you may receive another email before we are able to remove you.
